ACTWU's Research Department Records 5619/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- LDR - Atlantic Launderers and Cleaners, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- LDR - D.2.c - Atlantic Shirt Laundry Piece Rates, 1950-1952 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- LDR - Atlas Shirt Laundry, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- LDR - D.2.c - Bedford Piece Rates, 1941-1946 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- LDR - D.2.c - Benson Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- LDR - D.2.c - Best Service Piece Rates, 1946-1948 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- LDR - D.2.c - Blake Piece Rates, 1940-1951 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- LDR - D.2.c - Blue Diamond Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- LDR - Blue Point Laundry, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- LDR - Blue Point Laundry, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- LDR - Blue Point Laundry, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- LDR - D.2.c - Bon Piece Rates, 1940-1950 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- LDR - D.2.c - Brighton Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- LDR - D.2.c - Brighton Laundry Adjustment of Piece Rates, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- LDR - D.2.c - Brook Shirt Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- LDR - D.2.c - Brooklyn & Queens Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- LDR - D.2.c - Brookridge Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- LDR - F Carolyn Laundry Shirt Press Rates, 1946-1949 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- LDR - Carolyn Laundry - Washroom, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Apron Folding, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- LDR - F Cascade Laundry Apron String Tying and Napkin Counting, 1948-1949 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- LDR - F Cascade Laundry Assorters and Damp Assemblers, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - P.W. Markers Family Division, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry Classifiers' Problem, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Formative Coat Press, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry Linen Press - Formatic Coat Press, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Coat Press Formatic, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Coat Pressing, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Linen Press Earnings, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- LDR - F - Cascade Laundry Breakers, 1936-1946 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Coat Pressing, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Coat + Apron Folding Smocks + Coats, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- LDR - F - Cascade Laundry - Diaper Packers, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Diaper Folders, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- LDR - F - Cascade Laundry - District 50 Leaflets, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Assorters Pay, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- LDR - F - Cascade Laundry - Dry Cleaning Department, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Dry Cleaning Pressing, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Folder, Ironer #1, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Household Route Set-Up, 1951-1953 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Linen Press Rates, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Incorporation of Increases into Piece Rates, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 53)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Linen Press, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 54)
- LDR - F - Cascade Laundry - Napkin Folding, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- LDR - F - Cascade Laundry - Office Worker, 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 57)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Presses, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 58)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Pillowcase Ironer - Folder (Box 24, Folder 59)
- LDR - F - Cascade Laundry - Repair Department, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Shirt Pressing, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Soiled Counting Barber Towels, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 62)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - Soiled Goods Department, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- LDR - F - Cascade Laundry - Store Bundle Sorting, 1950-1951 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- LDR - Cascade Laundry - General Linen - Pants Press, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- LDR - D.2.c - Cashman Laundry Corporation - Piece rates, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 66)
- Central Laundry Service, Inc. Wages, Piece Rates, Individual Plants, 1945-1950 (Box 24, Folder 67)
- LDR - Champion Laundry Co. Wages, Piece Rates, Individual Plants, 1940-1950 (Box 24, Folder 68)
- LDR - Champion Laundry Co. - Formatic Short Press, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 69)
- LDR - Champion Laundry, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 70)
- LDR - D.2.c - Chasol Piece Rates, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- LDR - D.2.c - Clemente Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- LDR - D.2.c - Colonial Piece rates, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- LDR - F - Comet Laundry Piece Rate for Government Work, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- LDR - D.2.c - Colony Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- LDR - D.2.c - Comet Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- LDR - D.2.c - Community Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundries Corp. - Adjustment of Piece Rates, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. - Gold Seal, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp - Kent Ave, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- LDR - Consolidated - Unipress - Shirt Press, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- LDR - D.2.c - Consolidated Laundries Corp. Gold Seal Plant Piece Rates, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. Mayflower Piece Rates, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. Mayflower Press Dept., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentives, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentives, 1954-1955 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Plant Incentive Plan, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- LDR - F - Consolidated Laundry Corp. Mayflower - office workers, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- LDR - F - Consolidated Laundry Corp. Mayflower - Incentives, 1948-1952 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- LDR - F - Consolidated Laundry Corp. National - Incentives, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- LDR - D.2.c - Consolidated Laundry Corp. (Bronx) National Plant Piece Rates, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- LDR - Consolidated Laundry Corp. Bronx N.Y., 1952 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- LDR - D.2.c - Consolidated Laundry Corp. N.Y. Linen 32 St. Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- LDR - D.2.c - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- LDR - F - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 62 St. - Seniority, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- LDR - D.2.c - Consolidated Laundry Corp. NY Linen 94 St. Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- LDR - D.2.c - Consolidated Laundry Corp. Stancourt Plant Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- LDR - D.2.c - Cornell Shirt Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- LDR - D.2.c - Crescent Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Crib Diaper - Washroom - Change of Work Schedule, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Crib Diaper - Drivers - Disposables, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- LDR - D.2.c - Crown Heights Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Cupid, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- LDR - D.2.c - Dandy Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- LDR - Diebold's Shirt Laundry, Hillside, N.J. - Shirt Check Out - Not ACWA, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- LDR - Daniel's Steam Laundry, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- LDR - D.2.c - De Luxe Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- LDR - D.2.c - District Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- LDR - D.2.c - Domestic Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- LDR - D.2.c - Duplex Piece rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- LDR - D.2.c - Dyckman Piece Rates, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- LDR - F Empire Seal Laundry - Shirt operators, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- LDR - D.2.c - Eureka (Inwood Eureka) Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- LDR - D.2.c - Finest Piece Rates, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- LDR - Farmingdale Individual Laundry, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- LDR - Fox Square Laundry, 1946-1948 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- Minimum Wage - Federal, 1947-1951 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage Board (D.C.), 1946-1950 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- DC Minimum Wage (#2), 1951 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- D.C. Minimum Wage, 1949-1952 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage Board (Mass.), 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage - State, 1944-1950 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- State Labor Legislation, 1942-1949 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Clippings - FISA, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Clippings - FLSA, 1945-1949 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Congressional Comment, 1939-1948 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Reference Data, 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Minimum Wage (#3), 1945-1948 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Minimum Wage (#2), 1939-1947 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Minimum Wage (#1), 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Statements and Testimony - FLSA, 1937-1949 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Auerbach, 1939-1948 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage (#1), 1949 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Leather - Leather, Leather Goods and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee141-B), 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Children's Dress - Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Corsets, etc. - The Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 101-A), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Corsets, etc. - The Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 113-A), 1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Corsets, etc. - The Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 128-C), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Handkerchief, etc. - The Handkerchief, Scarf and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 101-D), 1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Handkerchief, etc. - The Handkerchief, Scarf and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 113-E), 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Sweater- The Sweater and Knit Swimwear industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 102-B), 1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Women's+Children's Underwear - The Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 102-A), 1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Women's+Children's Underwear - The Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 113-D), 1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Women's+Children's Underwear - The Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 128-A), 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Women's Outerwear - The Women's Outerwear, Needlework and Miscellaneous Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 101-C), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Women's Outerwear - The Women's Outerwear, Needlework and Miscellaneous Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 113-C), 1973 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Mergers and Sales Clippings, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Mergers and Sales Clippings, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Mergers and Sales Clippings, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Mergers and Sales Clippings, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Mergers and Sales Clippings, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Mergers and Sales Clippings, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Mergers and Sales Clippings, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Mergers and Sales Clippings, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Mexico - U.S. Border [Book 1/3] - Industrialization, 1963-1974 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Mexico - U.S. Border [Book 2/3] - Industrialization, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Mexico - U.S. Border [Book 1/3] - "Commuters" (Green Card Holders), 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Research File - Economic Trends Etc., 1947-1967 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Cuttings, 1954-1968 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Cuttings, 1969-1978 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Economic Conditions in the Male Apparel Industries, 1960-1967 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Economic Conditions in the Male Apparel Industries, 1968-1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- The Male Apparel Industries - Cuttings; Employment, Hours, and Earnings; And Imports, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Economic Conditions in the Male Apparel Industries, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Imports, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Imports 1965-1970 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Imports, 1971-1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Imports and Domestic Production of Major Items of Men's and Boys' Apparel/ Knit Shirts, 1958-1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Imports for Consumption and Domestic Production of Major Items etc., 1972-1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Imports for Consumption of Major Items etc., 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Imports as a Percentage of Domestic Production, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Mens & Boys' Apparel 1971 Compared with 1970, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- General Imports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Imports of Men's and Boys' Knit Shirts and Domestic Production of Men's and Boy's Knit Outerwear Sport Shirts, 1958-1971 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Leather Gloves Knit & Not Knit Fabric Gloves & Glove Linings, 1966-1971 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Men's & Boys' Neckties, 1964-1971 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Report on Degree of Import Penetration of Major Items of Men's & Boys' Apparel (Quarterly), 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- No. 1 - ACWA/ILGWU Economic Analysis of U.S. Apparel Industry and Imports, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  Inventory List of Numbered Files
- No. 151 - A Re-Evaluation of State Protective Legislation for Women Workers, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- No. 163 ACTWU/Potofsky Statements, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- No. 207 - Statement of Potofsky at Opening of CMA Negotiations, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- No. 232, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- No. 234, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- No. 235, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- No. 250 - Government Procurement - Third Quarter, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- No. 251 - Retail Sales, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- No. 252 - The Outlook for the Men's and Boys' Apparel Industries, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- No. 253 - Acquisitions and Mergers Reported From July-November, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- No. 254 - Profits and Sales of Major Male Apparel Manufacturing Companies, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- No. 258 - Imports as a Percentage of Domestic Production, Third Quarter, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  Inventory List of Numbered Files Imports as a Percentage of Domestic Production
- No. 259 - Imports as a Percentage of Domestic Production, January - September, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- No. 266 - Summary of major Men's and Boys' Apparel Imports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- No. 273 - Imports of Men's and Boys' Knit Shirts and Domestic Production of Men's and Boys' Knit Outerwear Sport Shirts, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- No. 275 - Quantities of Imports of Rubber and Plastic Gloves, 1966-1971 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- No. 276 - Quantities of Imports of Gloves and Glove Linings, By kind of Material, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- No. 277 - Quantities of Imports of Leather Gloves, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- No. 278 - Quantities of Imports of Knit and Not Knit Fabric Gloves and Glove Linings, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- No. 280 - Imports of Men's and Boys' Neckties, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- No. 291 - Data for the Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- No. 293 - Companies Controlling Major U.S. Manufacturers in the Cotton and Allied Industries, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- No. 294 - Revised List of Cotton Garment and Allied Companies, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- No. 296 - Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- No. 297 - Phillips-Van Heusen Plants, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- No. 298 - Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- No. 299 - Dollar Amount of Major Items of Men's Apparel Awarded by Government Contract, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- No. 305 - Meetings With Single Plants Employers, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- No. 311 - International Activities of Major Companies Operating in the Men's and Boys' Apparel Industries, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- No. 312 - Earnings and Labor Cost Data for Apparel Workers Abroad, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- No. 313 - Overseas Licensees of United States Male Apparel Companies, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- No. 323 - Statement by ALWJB for the Increases Effective November, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- No. 324 - Summary of Data on Imports and Domestic Production of Major Items of Men's and Boys' Apparel, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- No. 334 - Material for Clothing and Cotton Garment Meetings Next Week, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- No. 335 - No. of Establishments, Production Workers, Average Production Workers per Establishment in the Men's and Boy's Shirt/Nighwear Industry, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 36)
- No. 336 - No. of Establishments, Production Workers, Average Production Workers per Establishment in the Men's and Boy's Suit and Coat Industry, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 37)
- No. 341 - Performance Report: Wool and Man-Made Fiber Textiles, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 38)
- No. 347 - Survey of Men's Tailored Suit and Sport Coat Production, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 39)
- No. 350 - List of Pants Companies Contributing to the Amalgamated Insurance fund, By Joint Board and Type of Pants, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 40)
- No. 351 - List of Pants Companies Contributing to the Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, By Joint Board and Type of Pants, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 41)
- No. 354 - Master Copy, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 42)
- No. 356 - Overseas Licensing - Cotton Garment Industry, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 43)
- No. 357 - Data on Canadian Production, Imports, and Exports of Suits, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 44)
- No. 363 - Background Information for the Meeting of the GEB Subcommittee on Single Pants, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 45)
- No. 364 - Sales of Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 46)
- No. 368 - Material for Meeting of the GEB Subcommittee on Single Pants, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 47)
- No. 370 - Contract Expiration Dates of Major Companies, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 48)
- No. 378 - Overseas Licensees of United States Male Apparel Companies, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 49)
- No. 380 - Gross Payrolls and Manhours Study, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 50)
- No. 382 - Brand Names of Major U.S. Men's Clothing Manufacturers Under Contract with the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 51)
- No. 383 - Average Weekly Manhours for the Men's and Boys' Suit and Coat Industry, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 52)
- No. 384 - Selected Bibliography of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 53)
- No. 385 - Material in Connection with the Meeting with the Clothing Vice-Presidents on December 11th, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 54)
- No. 391 - Cost of Living Escalator Clause, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 55)
- No. 392 - Cost of Living Escalator Clause, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 56)
- No. 393 - Major Provisions of 1973 Agreement Between United Automobile Workers and Chrysler Corporation (Box 35, Folder 57)
- No. 395 - Dollar Amount of Major Items of Men's Apparel Awarded by Government Contract, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 58)
- No. 397 - Basic Data for the Clothing Industry Negotiations, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 59)
- No. 398 - Data for the Clothing Industry Negotiations, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 60)
- No. 402 - Companies Controlling Major United States Men's Clothing Manufacturers, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 61)
- No. 408 - The Immediate Outlook for the Male Apparel Industries, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 62)
- No. 409 - Cuttings; Employment, Hours, and Earnings; And Imports in the Male Apparel Industries, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 63)
- No. 419 - Organizing Gains for Retail Trade, All Areas, and Selected Joint Boards, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 64)
- No. 421 - Reports of Acquisitions and Mergers (other than retail) For Selected Companies in the Men's and Boys' Apparel and Related Industries, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 65)
- No. 422 - Estimated Number of Workers in Apparel Manufacturing Components, Under Contract with the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, in Selected Companies, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 66)
- No. 423 - Data for Meeting of Clothing Vice-Presidents on November 18, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 67)
- No. 424 - Apparel Plant Information (Box 35, Folder 68)
- No. 428 - Statement - The Apparel and Textile Industries to the AFL- CIO Board, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 69)
- No. 431 - Amalgamated Managers with Apparel Plants, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 70)
- No. 432 - Technical Note on the Benchmark Adjustments of the BLS Employment Data, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 71)
- No. 435 - Statement - The Apparel and Textile Industries to the AFL- CIO Board, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 72)
- No. 436 - Major Male Apparel Manufacturing Companies, Other than Tailored Clothing, in the US., 1975 (Box 35, Folder 73)
- No. 444 - Material for IUD Jobs Rally, April 26, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 74)
- No. 450 - Major Male Apparel Manufacturing Companies, Other than Tailored Clothing, in the US, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 75)
- No. 453 - Data for Negotiations - Liquidations and Plant Closings, 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 76)
- No. 454 - Outerwear Negotiations - Data on Products Produced by the Plants of Members of the National Outerwear Bargaining Committee, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 77)
- No. 461 - Shirt Negotiations - Date on Products Produced by the Plants of the Companies Represented by Drechsler & Leff, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 78)
- No. 462 - Pants Negotiations - Products Produced by Plants of Single Pants Companies Represented at the Meeting of July 22, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 79)
- No. 467 - Prehearing Statement on behalf of ACWA, AFL-CIO and ILGWU, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 80)
- No. 468 - Prehearing Statement on behalf of ACWA, AFL-CIO and ILGWU, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 81)
- No. 469 - Prehearing Statement on behalf of ACWA, AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 82)
  Inventory List of Numbered Files. Prehearing Statement on behalf of ACWA, AFL-CIO and ILGWU
- No. 470 - Prehearing Statement on behalf of ACWA, AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 83)
- No. 471 - Some Long-Run Trends in the Men's Clothing Industry, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 84)
- No. 472 - Statement of the ACWA, AFL-CIO on the Need for a $3.00 Federal Minimum Wage, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 85)
- No. 474 - ACWA Plants Making Sport Coats and Leisure Wear, Men's and Boys' Clothing Industry (Box 35, Folder 86)
- No. 475 - ACWA Plants Making Leisure Suits by Industry and Region (Box 35, Folder 87)
- No. 478 - Comparison of the Two Series on Male Apparel Imports, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 88)
- No. 483 Long-Run Trends in the Shirt Industry, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 89)
- No. 483 The Male Apparel and Textile Industries, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 90)
- No. 490 - Pants List for Negotiations, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 91)
- No. 491 - Material for Negotiations, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 92)
- No. 492 - Shirt Negotiations, Dress Shirts and Sports Shirts, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plans, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 93)
- No. 517 - Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 94)
- General Economic Conditions, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 95)
- General Economic Conditions, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 96)
- General Economic Conditions, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 97)
- General Economic Conditions, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 98)
- General Economic Conditions, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 99)
- General Economic Conditions, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 100)
- NLRB Elections (Prepared by Research for GEB Meetings), 1953-1976 (Box 35, Folder 101)
- Collective Bargaining Agreements (Prepared by Research for GEB Meetings), 1955-1976 (Box 35, Folder 102)
- Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1976-1970 (Box 35, Folder 103)
- Recognition Agreement (Apparel), 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 104)
- NLRB Elections - Male Apparel, 1970-1976 (Box 35, Folder 105)